Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1957-1991, Bulk: 1982-1990.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 68th Session, 1973-1988; 3
  - Correspondence, 1982-1985; 1
    - General (6 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - General (7 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - General (8 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - General (9 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - General (10 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - General (11 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - General (12 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - General (13 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - General (14 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - General (15 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - General (16 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - General (17 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - General (18 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - General (19 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - General (20 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - General (21 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - General (22 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - High Technology (1 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - High Technology (2 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - High Technology (3 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Highways and Roads (1 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Highways and Roads (2 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Highways and Roads (3 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Highways and Roads (4 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - HVAC Licensing, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Health, Acupuncture, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Health, Deaf and Blindness (1 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Health, Deaf and Blindness (2 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Health, Deaf and Blindness (3 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Health, General (1 of 8), 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Health, General (2 of 8), 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Health, General (3 of 8), 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Health, General (4 of 8), 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Health, General (5 of 8), 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Health, General (6 of 8), 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Health, General (7 of 8), 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Health, General (8 of 8), 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Health, Health Facilities, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Health, Home Health, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Health, Licensed Dietician’s Act, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Health, Podiatry, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Health, Optometry, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Health, Nurse Practice Act, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Health Spa Act, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Housing (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Housing (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Immigration, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Industrial Accident Board, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Industrial and Mechanical Bills, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Insurance, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Interest and Dividends Withholding, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Lemon Law, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Libraries, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Limestone County Road Law, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Limestone County Senior Citizens Center, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Marriage and Family, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Mental Health (1 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Mental Health (2 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Mental Health (3 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Midlothian Trade Zone, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Milk, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Native Americans, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Occupational Therapy Act, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Oil and Gasoline (1 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Oil and Gasoline (2 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Oil and Gasoline (3 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Oil and Gasoline (4 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Peveto Tax Bill, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Physical and Occupational Therapy and Athletic Training Combined Boards (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Physical and Occupational Therapy and Athletic Training Combined Boards (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Physical and Occupational Therapy and Athletic Training Combined Boards (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Police and Fire, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Pot Hole Bill, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Public Utilities Commission and Rates (1 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Public Utilities Commission and Rates (2 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Public Utilities Commission and Rates (3 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Public Utilities Commission and Rates (4 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (1 of 14), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (2 of 14), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (3 of 14), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (4 of 14), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (5 of 14), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (6 of 14), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (7 of 14), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (8 of 14), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (9 of 14), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (10 of 14), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (11 of 14), 1983 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (12 of 14), 1983 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (13 of 14), 1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (14 of 14), 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Professional Services Tax, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Recreational Property Tax, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Registry Bill, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Religious Liberty, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Self-Insurance Worker’s Compensation, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Senate Renovation, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Sexual Orientation, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Sign Ordinances and Outdoor Advertising, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Sin Taxes, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Small Business, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Social Security, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Social Worker’s Certification Act, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Solid Waste, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Speech Pathology, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - State Employees Insurance and Benefits (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - State Employees Insurance and Benefits (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - State Programs and Economic Assistance, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Taxes, General, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Teen Pregnancy, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Texas Flag Student Letters, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Thank You and Congratulations (1 of 9), 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Thank You and Congratulations (2 of 9), 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Thank You and Congratulations (3 of 9), 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Thank You and Congratulations (4 of 9), 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Thank You and Congratulations (5 of 9), 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Thank You and Congratulations (6 of 9), 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Thank You and Congratulations (7 of 9), 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Thank You and Congratulations (8 of 9), 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Thank You and Congratulations (9 of 9), 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Transportation (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Transportation (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Trucking Deregulation (1 of 7), 1983 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Trucking Deregulation (2 of 7), 1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Trucking Deregulation (3 of 7), 1983 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Trucking Deregulation (4 of 7), 1983 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Trucking Deregulation (5 of 7), 1983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Trucking Deregulation (6 of 7), 1983 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Trucking Deregulation (7 of 7), 1983 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Tuition Equalization, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Unemployment, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Utilities, General, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Various House and Senate Bills (1 of 4), 1982-1985 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Various House and Senate Bills (2 of 4), 1982-1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Various House and Senate Bills (3 of 4), 1982-1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Various House and Senate Bills (4 of 4), 1982-1985 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Veterans, 1983-1984 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Video Rentals, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Wage Law, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Water Resources, 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Wild Free-Roaming Horse and Burro Act, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Senate Bills, 1981-1985; 2
    - Child Safety Seats: S.B. 6 Fact Sheet, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Community College Funds: S.B. 1332 and 1333, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Direct Payment Permit: S.B. 541, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - DWI License Suspension, Bill Synopsis: S.B. 1, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Education, ISD’s and Community Colleges: S.B. 675, 1982-1985 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Education Bills: Legislative Summaries, 1983-1985 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Education Reform: Clippings and Summaries, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Education Reform: Information and Revisions Binder, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Education Reform: Permanent University Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Education Reform: Resources, 1983-1985 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Education: S.B. 1014 University of Texas of the Permian Basin, Fiscal Note, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Education Reform: Teacher Certification News clippings, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Education Reform: Teacher Certification Summaries, 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Education Reform: Teacher Merit Pay News clippings, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Education Reform: Teacher Merit Pay Research (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Education Reform: Teacher Merit Pay Research (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Election Code, Ballot Tabulation Bill and Notes: S.B. 51, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Election Code: Caucus System Problems, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Election Code: Concerns, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Election Code: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Election Code: Democratic National Convention Information, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Election Code: Democratic National Convention Information, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Election Code: Democratic National Convention Party Rules, 1984 February 14 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Election Code: Election Law and Voter Handbooks, 1983-1984, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Election Code: Election Law and Voter Handbooks, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Election Code: Memos, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Election Code: News clippings, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Election Code: News clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Election Code: Notes and Information, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Election Code: Outgoing Correspondence, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Election Code: Petition to End Caucus System, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Election Code: Primary/Caucus Revision, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Election Code: Response Letters, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Election Code: Response Letters, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Election Code Revision Bill, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, 1984 January (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, 1984 August (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, 1984 September 25-26 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, 1984 September 26 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, 1984 October 10 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, 1984 October 23 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tape One, 1984 November 13 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tape Two, 1984 November 13 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tapes Three and Four, 1984 November 13 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tape One, 1984 November 14 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tapes Two and Three, 1984 November 14 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tapes One and Two, 1984 December 4 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tapes Three and Four, 1984 December 4 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tapes Five and Six, 1984 December 5 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tapes One and Two, 1984 December 18 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tapes One and Two, 1985 January 11 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee Tape Three, 1985 January 11 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, 1985 February 8 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1984 December 4 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, Meeting Notes and Minutes (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, Meeting Notes and Minutes (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, Meeting Notes and Minutes (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Election Code: Revision Committee, Meeting Notes and Minutes, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Election Code: Revision Materials, 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Election Code: Statements and Notes, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Election Code: Study Committee (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Election Code: Study Committee (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Election Code: Study Committee (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Election Code: Witness Cards, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Ethics Commission: Analysis and Reviews, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Ethics Commission: Memos and Drafts, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Ethics Commission: News clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Ethics Commission: Other State Information (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Ethics Commission: Other State Information (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Ethics Commission: Other State Questionnaires (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Ethics Commission: Other State Questionnaires (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Farm Workers’ Compensation: S.B. 338 Information and Correspondence, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Health and Human Services: Coordinating Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Health and Human Services: Health Issues and Research, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Highway Funding: S.B. 287, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Lemon Laws: S.B. 1141 Research, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Midlothian Trade Zone Corporation: S.B. 769, 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Municipal Annexations: S.B. 1077 Analysis and Research, 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Oil and Tax Reform: S.B. 342 Research and Reports, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Public School Finance: Correspondence: S.B. 391, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Taxes: S.B. 37 Jones Tax Bill, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Utilities Deregulation: Correspondence and Background (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Utilities Deregulation: Correspondence and Background (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Utilities Deregulation: Notes and Articles, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Utilities Deregulation: S.B. 553, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Utilities Deregulation: S.B. 232 Edwards Amendment, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Utilities Deregulation: S.B. 232 Notes and Information, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Veterans’ Land Board and Housing Assistance: S.B. 408 and Revisions, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Veterans’ Land Board and Housing Assistance Research and Notes, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Senate Resolutions, 1983-1984; 3
    - Bill Hickey, DeSoto: S.R. 656, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Capitol Restoration: S.R. 68, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Senate Proclamations, A.B. (Jep) Sims, Limestone County, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Retirement System Investments: S.C.R. 25, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Special Committee on Business, Technology, and Education: S.R. 3, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - House Bills, 1983-1988; 4
    - Barbering: H.B. 1010 Correspondence, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Deceptive Trade Practices Act: H.B. 1438, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Deviate Sexual Conduct: H.B. 2138, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Education, Amendments, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Education, Committee for Finance and Programs, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Education, Committees for Students, Personnel, and Long-Range Planning, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Education, District 9, News clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Education, District 9, Memos and Research, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Education, Funding Estimates, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Education, Legislative Report, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Education, Meeting Notes, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Education, Newsletters and Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Education, Proposals to Select Committee on Public Education (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Education, Proposals to Select Committee on Public Education (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Education, Public Education Reform: H.B. 72, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Education, Resources, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Education, Scholarships Notes and Memos, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Education, State Board Appointments, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Education, State Board Education Districts, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Education, State Board of Education Committees, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Education, State Plan for Adult Education, 1986-1988 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Education, State Plan for Vocational Education, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Education, Teacher Education Information, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Education, Teacher Education News clippings, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Bill Analysis, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Budget Data (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Budget Data (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Budget Estimates, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Issues Document (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Issues Document (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Education: H.B. 72, News clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Education: H.B. 72, News clippings (1 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Education: H.B. 72, News clippings (2 of 2), 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Rules to Implement, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Statements and Positions, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Summaries and Changes, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Education: H.B. 72, Vote Sheets, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Elderly Rights: H.B. 1726, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Health Inspector Code of Conduct Repeal: H.B. 103, Analysis and Information, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Code: H.B. 1961 and Research, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Investment Funds: H.B. 1046, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Nursing Home Inspections: H.B. 225, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Public Employee Protection: H.B. 1075, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Tax Code: H.B. 122, 4.5 Cent Compromise, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Tax Code: Advertising Tax Information and Correspondence, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Tax Code: Auto Registration Fees, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Tax Code: H.B. 122 Bill Analysis and Fiscal Note, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Tax Code: Computer Software Amendment, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Tax Code: H.B. 122 Edwards’ One Cent Amendment, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Tax Code: H.B. 122 Edwards/Lyon Floor Substitute, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Tax Code: Grant Jones H.B. 122 Amendment, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Tax Code: H.B. 122 House Version, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Tax Code: Standard Industrial Classification Services, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Tax Code: H.B. 122 Summary and Final Amendment, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Tax Code: Tax Bill Proposals Comparison, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Tax Code: Telecommunications Amendment, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Tax Code: Transportation Tax Data, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Topical, 1980-1985; 5
    - Citizens, Chamber of Commerce: Duncanville, 1983-1985 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Citizens, General: Corsicana, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Citizens, General: McLennan County, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Commerce, Labor and Economic Development, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Day Care Licensing, 1984-1985 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Defense Industry, Fiscal Notes Newsletter, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Economic Development Administration, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Education: Rice Junior High Senate Proclamations, Corsicana, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Education, Select Committee on Public Education, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Elderly and Aging, Department on Aging Legislative Summary, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Elderly and Aging, Long Term Care, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Election, Presidential Primary Reconfiguration, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Election, Presidential Primary Tabulation, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Ethylene Dibromide (EDB): Background Material for EDB Hearing Notebook, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Ethylene Dibromide: Memos and Testimonies, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Ethylene Dibromide (EDB): Research, Notes, News clippings, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Employment, Industrial Development, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Employment, Job Training Partnership Act Overview, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Employment, Work Incentive Program, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, Public Utility Commission Affirmative Action Plan, 1984, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Farming: Soil and Water Conservation Board Directory, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Policy: Case Study, Corsicana, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Health, Acupuncture, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Health, Optical Practices, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Health Care, Therapists and Athletic Trainers Correspondence, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Human Resources, Government Programs, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Hunger: Senate Interim Committee on Hunger and Nutrition Report, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Infrastructure: Corsicana, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Infrastructure: District 9 Highways, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Infrastructure: Limestone County, News clippings, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Infrastructure: McLennan County Coal Pipeline, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Infrastructure: Midlothian Highways, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Limestone Road Law, Notes, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Open Beaches Policy Information, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Prosecutor Council Sunset Advisory Self-Evaluation Report, Part II, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Public Utilities Commission, Amendment and Remarks, 1983 April 6 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Redistricting, Amendment and Notes, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Redistricting, Analyses, Notes, and Maps, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Redistricting, Background, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Redistricting, Duncanville Resolution, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Redistricting, Maps and District Analysis Reports (1 of 4), 1983 (Box 47, Folder 7)